Ha…
Puffa…
Oh, It's a sunrise, the sky of the starry sky
The sky with a new light
I'm all alone
I think that's why I'm going to the picnic
No matter if you're with me or not, you'll never forget
Of course, always with you
I'm going to take you with me, but I'm afraid you'll fall
That's right, happy I'm not with you
If I could, I would have been the same as Oten
The time when I closed my eyes
There will be a smile on your lips
You and you, you and you
If you love me, if you love me
I will be the same as the heart
I will be the same as the time when I opened my eyes
...um...
Maybe it's me
If I could have realized the time machine,
there would have been completely different,
we were so far apart from the world we were together
Maybe I could have come back or come back to the world
If I could have come back or come back
I wouldn't have used that
But I was able to find a way for my family
to get close to me
and I'm able to have fun with my friends
A river from the river.
I can't find any place where I can hide.
Who was that feeling?
What?
Is that a meeting?
We can't hide it from you either.
What's wrong?
I can't do anything!
What's that attitude?
Where are you hiding?
Is it still there?
This time we have a tail.
Where are you hiding?
What are you doing?
There is!
You are not eating my food, are you?
What are you doing in such a place?
I like it. Look at this.
There's something inside.
I wonder if it's a hand.
My father and my mother are going home.
Don't touch me, Tegami! What are you doing here?
Bien came to see the river.
That's why he was angry.
Is there anyone in the river?
I think there are people who came to see this island the same way.
That person is alone.
That's why Tegami was angry.
That's right.
You're the other person who came to see the river.
I don't want to see it.
Don't you think so?
Don't you forget about what you saw?
I can't forget about the people who came to see me.
Tegami.
It was a bad idea.
I don't want to go to the river if it's like this.
Oh, you're thinking about it.
I'm thinking about it because I'm old.
I'm thinking about the river that's going to be a great deal to see the river.
A great deal?
I think it's a good idea to see the river that's going to be a great deal to see the river.
I think there might be people around us.
Where is that great deal?
I think there's a great deal to see.
Is there anyone who came to see me again?
I think it would be nice to meet someone who's not interested in going today.
That's right.
I think there's someone who's not interested to see me again.
If you tell me there is a way, your luck will come out.
Whoa, that's right.
That's right.
How about an online events?
How about you, Minos?
How about you then come back to this place?
We're not going to search for people.
I'm going to die.
You're a fool.
Who's going to be here?
Everyone's here.
Don't be so serious.
Are we going to run away?
I've been there for three years.
I'm going to do that.
I'll tell you when I read it.
What's the matter?
My father and mother are both home.
They're not here.
This is the hand that a person lives in the river.
It's not like that.
There's no one here.
Everyone, there's no time to waste.
All right.
Let's go!
I'm going to die.
I can't live like this.
Who's going to die?
I can't handle it.
What if there's a enemy?
I'm going to die.
I can't handle the enemy.
I can't handle it.
I'm going to die.
Rank.
Rank, when I was going to die,
did you remember what I said before?
I'm sorry for your brother.
Anyway, let's go to Lanka!
Let's get started!
That's amazing.
Do you see anything?
It's jungle.
What kind of people are there?
I'm scared.
Now, let's go!
We'll find a person who can easily get along with the army!
Let's do it!
Let's go home!
I'm feeling like I'm going to be like this from now on!
What?
I'm scared of the army!
Yes.
Please don't do that.
I'm a little bit scared of the army!
No!
I'm scared of the army!
I'm scared!
The army is here!
I'm scared of the army!
That's amazing!
I'm scared too!
I'm scared of the army!
What are you doing here?
I'm going to find the army first!
I'm scared.
I'm scared of the army!
Let's do this!
I won't let you get away from me!
What should I do, Ryanka-san?
I won't let you help me, if you want to.
Let's go, let's go.
What's going on here?
I'm in trouble, right?
Let's go!
Help me, Ryanka!
If you win, I'll help you, Tsuru-san!
Well, if you look at the back a little bit...
The back?
Oh, thank you!
Thank you!
I'm so proud of myself!
Don't you think you're an adult?
That's not what I meant!
Thank you!
It's okay!
Ah!
I'm so proud of you!
I want to see you save me!
If you say so, I'll see you.
That's right!
I'm the kind of person who makes you feel like it's a beauty!
I'm still alive.
But I've never been able to do it for a long time.
I was thinking about it after the morning.
Are you alive?
It's really busy.
Everything I do has to be alright,
and I'm so proud of myself!
It's a good thing, I'm not a big fan of you.
What?
Then, Gajah!
Come here with your girlfriend!
That's not true, Mr. Dothomos.
From now on, you'll have to take care of your body.
What are you saying?
It's just a lie!
Stop it!
It's not dangerous today!
Hey!
Stop it!
It's dangerous!
It's not a lie!
Stop it!
Hey!
What's wrong?
Stop it!
From now on, you'll have to take care of your body.
Is it time?
This is the time of the river's name!
It's time to leave!
I'll just leave it alone!
It's a secret!
I hope I can go soon!
Mr. Dothomos, please take care of your body.
Oh, I'm feeling a little tired.
I'm feeling a little tired.
How I can catch the fish?
If you want to separate it from this, let's talk about it.
You didn't get to see a person like we are in a possible state.
A person...?
If you said you want to see a woman in this 1000 years
If you said I want to see the woman in this 1000 years
If you said you want to see her
What does a person in the 1000 years
A person in the 1000 years
Will you understand?
What kind of creature is this?
That makes me happy!
I wonder if you've been listening to me for a long time,
so let's listen to that.
Since you've been listening to me for a long time,
I'm sure you'll understand.
Where are you going?
There's no choice but to be with you.
You're not tired, are you?
I was born to be a kid, so I'm not going to return it.
No, I'm not going to return it.
I'm waiting for the enemy's dog to return it to me.
I'm not going to return it until I find the dog that I've been looking for.
I'm going to put it in the bag.
No, that's not how it is.
Huh?
It's amazing!
I can't see anything.
What are you doing?
It's a trap.
Choro-san might be living in that trap.
That's right.
I'm going to return it to you, so I'm going to return it to you.
Choro-san, please don't do that.
Choro-san, please don't do that too.
Let's try again.
I can't wait anymore.
I guess there's someone in this trap.
Someone in this trap is like nobody.
There're people in this trap.
It's not like that.
I'm going to look for the dog.
What?
It's a child.
What did you do?
I was a little surprised.
I'm sorry, Kamen!
Kamen, are you not a human being like us?
I'm a really cool person.
Hiram!
Don't you know?
I'm sorry.
So, tell us about this.
Why did you suddenly appear in the library?
That's not true, Hiram!
It's not a big deal, isn't it?
I'm sorry!
This is getting smaller!
What's going on?
It's getting smaller, isn't it?
Hey, are we going to return to the real world?
We're going to return, aren't we?
Hiram!
Well, what's the most important thing for you to do?
Don't do that!
I'm going to take the stone to the stone!
Superb!
Oh!
Oh, no!
Hey, you!
Did you get hit by the stone wall?
There's a way to get the stone to the stone wall!
That's why you're going to have to do that!
No, I didn't.
I didn't have to do anything to get the stone to the stone wall.
Let's look for a solution tomorrow.
Yeah.
Muka Muka, there's a person like us who are in this place.
Mya Muka!
I don't even know what to do.
Huh? Muka Muka?
Where?
Ah, Muka Muka! Muka Muka!
Muka Muka! Muka Muka!
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka! Muka Muka! Muka Muka!
Muka Muka! Muka Muka!
Muka Muka, what do you think?
Muka Muka! Muka! Muka!
I knew it was Muka Muka!
Huh? Is that Muka Muka a doctor?
Muka! Muka! Muka!
Muka Muka, you're kind.
I think Muka is going to come home when I see this.
I want to be your father-in-law.
I have something important to do.
But I can't say anything like that to you.
I'm doing my best to be your father-in-law.
What are you doing?
Why are you looking for someone?
That's why...
What are you doing?
Yesterday, I was searching for someone.
If someone's there, I'll ask them to come and ask them to come.
Is there anyone here?
Then, where are you going?
Um...
I went to the hospital and went back to the hospital.
That's right.
Are you going to be your father-in-law?
No, that's not what I meant.
I found you.
You were looking for someone to come and ask them to come.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my dear.
I was told that you're going to be my father-in-law.
Oh, no! I'm not your father-in-law.
Oh, no!
That's not what I meant.
I'm not going to be your father-in-law.
Now, I'm going to be your father-in-law.
I'm going to be your father-in-law.
You're just to move over for a while.
What!
That's why!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I've forgotten about the names of my friends.
Did you say anything to your brothers?
No, I'm not.
Well, I'll just leave them to you.
If I say anything, the smell will go away.
That's why you can't sleep.
Oh, I want to meet you here and the people here.
Is he really here?
What's happening?
He's moving the vehicle.
A rare animal that came from the Edo's army!
The Edo's army?
Oh, that's a little too much!
It's a man who was born and raised in a dangerous universe,
but this is a rare animal!
Do you want to be able to be with the Edo's army?
Yes, I do.
The human being of the Edo's army was born here!
Where is he?
He's already back to the Edo's army.
Huh? He's back?
But there's a way to return!
Wow, I can't even go back!
I can't even go back!
You can't even go back!
Didn't you hear that?
That's a rare animal!
If you keep going up your neck, you'll be able to go back!
What's the point of meeting with the Edo's army?
You bastard!
Let me go!
What's the point of meeting with the Edo's army?
You've got to go back!
It was so dirty.
Where is it? How did that people go?
Ahoyannna.
We should look anywhere like this.
The thing that could be done is the core.
If you look at the core you can also change them?
Yes.
At that time people were using an electric machine to move away.
The white light of the sea is reflected in the eyes of that man.
And the water and the fire are also in the heart.
What does it mean that we have come to the sea?
Then, if we get to the point, we can go back to the shop.
That's right.
I think we should go right away.
What should we do?
I think I'll have to go back to my home.
What is it?
Oh!
It's time for a new journey!
Even if it's too big, it'll be bigger than this size!
Hey!
Mizumi!
If you go back to the water, you'll be able to stop!
Hurry and get back!
I understand.
I'll be able to...
get back to the water!
I won't!
No!
It's moving!
What's going on?
Did you think it was a sound?
Hey, Kame-san!
What kind of eyes do we have?
I don't know.
You taught me that, right?
It's because of Kamedo.
I thought about what I had to do.
It's hard to think about it, but...
It's good to have hope.
If you give up your eyes, you'll be able to get back to the water.
Then, I'll be able to think about what I had to do.
That's why I'm here.
I'm coming back to the water of the Kamedo.
Translated by Releska
and the price of our daily life
in the future
we'll always be in the same room
they're all the same
what's the thing that's always moving around
Whatever it is, the
Bay of the
Love, love Love, love, love, love, love
Janity, love, please
I carefully dis wellness
To Christmas
Manzan Aden
I came to the village with my mate but this place is in no good condition!
You are doing a great job!
That's the project of a local tu卓遊!
Why so much?
I'm at the limit today.
I wanted to get lost in the engine,
but maybe because I know there is no other place in the city.
Next time, I'll be with you.
I'll be with you, with you, with you, with you, with you!